game-debate.com 2019-03-21

# Game Debate Privacy Statement

## Introduction

Security & Privacy is an important part of our platform that we take very seriously. Therefore, this Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Game-Debate collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the https://game-debate.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products or services offered by Game-Debate.

In order to ensure confidentiality and lawful processing of its, Visitors, Customers and Users personal data, Game-Debate in its capacity of a data controller and of a processor, conducts its activities in strict compliance with the requirements set in the (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of this data (GDPR).

This Privacy Policy applies to all Customers, Users and Visitors of our Site and Services.

What Information We Collect and How We Use It 

We may collect the following types of information about you on our Website

###  Customers and Visitors of our Site 

We may collect your personal data in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our Site, register on the Site, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form, or in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available.

Registration and Contact Information: As appropriate and depending on the Services you would like to use, Customers and Visitors may be asked to provide us with full name, username, email, address, credit card, phone number or billing information.

Technical, Usage and Location Information: We automatically collect information on how you interact with the Site, such as the IP address from which you access the Site, date and time, information about your browser, operating system and computer or device, pages viewed and items clicked. We may also collect location information, including location information automatically provided by your computer or device. We use cookies and similar technologies to collect some of this information to maintain persistent login to our Site.

Third Party Platforms. We may collect information when you interact with our advertisements and other content on third-party sites or platforms, such as social networking sites. This may include information such as Facebook Likes, profile information gathered from social networking sites during signup or the fact that you viewed or interacted with our content.

Other Information. We may collect other information from you that is not specifically listed here. We may use any such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy or as otherwise permitted by you.

##  Cookies 

Our Site uses both first and third party Cookies to enhance User experience. A User's web browser places a cookie on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert when cookies are being sent. If they do so, please note that some parts of the Site and Campaigns may cease to function.

##  How We Use Collected Information 

Game-Debate may collect and use User's personal information for the following purposes:

### Game-Debate Website Users

  * To administer our Website and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  * To write or display content such as case studies or customer testimonials on our Site;
  * To improve Game-Debate to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your Device;
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * To send periodic emails: We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their subscription. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
  * Analyze anonymized statistics or usage to help improve the Game-Debate platform

##  Sharing Information With Third Parties 

We do not access, sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. 

###  Third Party Websites 

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

##  Legal Disclosures 

In certain limited circumstances, we may also have to disclose your personal data to public authorities and other third parties, if the disclosure is in response to lawful requests made by such public authorities, including to conform with national security or law enforcement requirements. Your personal information may also be disclosed to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities or required by law or regulation including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas.

Game-Debate may also share personal data with third parties to prevent, investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service or any other agreement related to the Services, or as otherwise required by law.

##  Jurisdiction and Legality of Content 

Publication of information found on Game-Debate may be in violation of the laws of the country or jurisdiction from where you are viewing this information. The Game-Debate database is stored on a server in the UK and is maintained in reference to the protections afforded under local law. Laws in your country or jurisdiction may not protect or allow the same kinds of speech or distribution. Game-Debate does not encourage the violation of any laws, and cannot be responsible for any violations of such laws should you link to this domain or use, reproduce, or republish the information contained herein.

##  Information Security 

We use appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect any personal information we process about visitors to our Website against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, please note that no Internet transmission can ever be guaranteed 100% secure, and so we encourage you to take care when disclosing personal information online and to use readily available tools, such as Internet firewalls, secure e-mail and similar technologies to protect yourself online.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Game-Debate uses Braintree and Paypal to process our credit card payments and no credit card details are stored on our servers. Braintree and Paypal have been audited by a PCI-certified auditor, and is certified to PCI Service Provider Level 1. This is the most stringent level of certification available.

In case of an unauthorized security intrusion that materially affects you Game-Debate will notify you as soon as possible and will within reasonable time report the action we took in response.

##  EU and EEA residents 

The servers where Game-Debate stores all personal data are located in the EU. If you are located in any country outside the EU or the EEA, please be aware that any information provided to us, including personal information, will be transferred from your country of origin to the EU. Except in the case of data transfers under the EU-US Privacy Shield and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield, we may ask for your express consent to provide such data to us or allow us to collect such data. 

##  International Transfer of Personal Data 

All personal data we process is stored directly, without any subsequent transfers, on EU-based servers, which we loan from a third-party datacenter that is certified and adheres to the EU – Privacy Shield Framework.

To additionally guarantee to our users the legality of our processing services and the international transfers of the personal data, Game-Debate has undertaken GDPR compliant contractual commitments, binding us, as a data processor, to protect the data privacy and to ensure the most adequate level of data security. 

Please note that the country where we operate may have privacy and data protection laws that differ from, and are potentially less protective than, the laws of your country. You agree to this risk when you create an account with Us and click "I accept Game-Debate’s Terms of Service & Privacy Policy" to data transfers, irrespective of which country you live in. If you later wish to withdraw your consent, you can delete your Game-Debate account as described in the "Your Rights" section. 

###  Privacy Controls & Choices 

Game-Debate Website Communication: Our Site Visitors and Users have a choice about how we use their personal data to get in touch with them and may choose to opt-out at any time by unsubscribing or changing their account settings. 

Your Rights: We provide all Customers, Visitors and Users of our Site with the opportunity to request access, correction, restriction, deletion, data portability or oppose to any personal information that has previously been provided to us in connection with the use of our Website, as required by law. You can send us an email to privacy@game-debate.com. We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity.

### Game-Debate's Data Protection Officer

Game-Debate has a Data Protection Officer who is responsible for matters relating to privacy and data protection. This Data Protection Officer can be reached at the following address:

Game-Debate

Attn: Data Protection Officer

14 King Square,

Bristol,

BS2 8JH

privacy@game-debate.com

##  Business Transfers 

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Game-Debate, or substantially all of its assets were to be acquired, or in the unlikely event that Game-Debate goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquire of Game-Debate or its assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy. 

##  Changes To This Privacy Policy 

Game-Debate has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

##  Your Acceptance Of These Terms 

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

##  Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at privacy@game-debate.com 

###  This document was last updated on May 10th, 2018
